Anjali Ajay Dofe

SY B.Tech Student Pune, Maharashtra, India August 19, 2020 dofeaa19.comp@coep.ac.in linkedin.com/in/anjali-dofe-0a126b1a1

Education

College of Engineering Pune (COEP)

B. Tech Computer Engineering

Indian School Al-Ghubra (ISG)

Class 11-12 CBSE (Science with Economics)

- Prefect, a part of school's Prefectorial Body
- Scored 95.8% in Class 12 Boards Exam

Pune, Maharashtra 2019 - 2023 Muscat, Oman 2017 - 2019

Personal Statement

I'm a hard working person and give my best and do the work assigned to me with utmost dedication. My qualities include patience, hard work and dedication. I have experience of working in FOSSMEET from over the past 8 months and I am also a part of COEP MITRA as I believe mental well being is also equally important as academics and physical health, and I look forward to expanding my horizons and am open to accepting new opportunities. In fact, I'm such an amazing person that you would never regret and be happy if you hire me.

Experience

FOSSMEET

Coordinator Jan, 2020 - Present

- Media

- Content Creation

Round Square Activities

Volunteer

- Organizing and managing Fundraisers

Muscat, Oman May 2018 - March 2019

Awards & Honours

Class 12 Economics Topper in Oman
Victor Ludorum (Academics)
Victor Ludorum in Music
Madhyama Poorna in Hindustani Classical Music(Keyboard)
Best Speaker at MMUN and Speaker Representative at FAO Headquarters, Rome 2016

Skills

• Programming and Markup Languages

Beginner: C, LatexIntermediate: Python

• Software

Intermediate: MS Powerpoint, MS Excel, MS Word
Beginner: MATLAB, Scilab, GNUPLOT, Github

 \bullet Other

- Keyboard Player, Delegate Speaker, Volunteer, Social Worker